Guide to the University of Utah football video collection 1948-1999
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Coach's films: plays, practice, highlights and games, 1986 (Box 46)
  - Utah vs. Ohio State kicking, 1986 September 27; 16mm film (Reel 1052)
- Coach's films: games, 1986 (Box 47)
  - Utah vs. Ohio State kicking, 1986 September 27; 16mm film (Reel 1053)
  - Utah vs. Ohio State offense, 1986 September 27; 16mm film (Reel 1054-1057)
  - Utah vs. Ohio State defense, 1986 September 27; 16mm film (Reel 1058-1061)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, 1986 October 03; 16mm film (Reel 1062-1067)
  - Utah vs. Air Force defense, 1986 October 03; 16mm film (Reel 1068-1073)
  - Utah vs. Air Force kicking, 1986 October 03; 16mm film (Reel 1074-1076)
- Coach's films: games, 1986 (Box 48)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1986 October 11; 16mm film (Reel 1077-1081)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1986 October 11; 16mm film (Reel 1082-1087)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1986 October 11; 16mm film (Reel 1088-1089)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1986 October 18; 16mm film (Reel 1090-1094)
    Reels 1-3, 2-3, 3-3, 1-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1986 October 18; 16mm film (Reel 1095-1098)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico kicking, 1986 October 18; 16mm film (Reel 1099-1100)
- Coach's films: games, 1986 (Box 49)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1986 October 18; 16mm film (Reel 1101)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State offense, 1986 October 25; 16mm film (Reel 1102-1104)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State defense, 1986 October 25; 16mm film (Reel 1105-1106)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State kicking, 1986 October 25; 16mm film (Reel 1107-1108)
- Coach's films: games, 1986 (Box 50)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State defense, 1986 October 25; 16mm film (Reel 1109-1111)
    Reels 1-2, 1-2, 1-2
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, 1986 November 01; 16mm film (Reel 1112-1117)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii defense, 1986 November 01; 16mm film (Reel 1118-1123)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii kicking, 1986 November 01; 16mm film (Reel 1124-1126)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, 1986 November 08; 16mm film (Reel 1127-1129)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State kicking, 1986 November 08; 16mm film (Reel 1130-1132)
- Coach's films: games, 1986 (Box 51)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, 1986 November 08; 16mm film (Reel 1133)
    Reels 1-2
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1986 November 08; 16mm film (Reel 1134-1142)
    Reels 1-2, 1-2, 1-2, 1-2, 2-2, 2-2, 2-2, 2-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1986 November 15; 16mm film (Reel 1143-1146)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1986 November 15; 16mm film (Reel 1147-1150)
  - Utah vs. Utah State kicking, 1986 November 15; 16mm film (Reel 1151-1152)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1986 November 22; 16mm film (Reel 1153-1154)
  - Utah vs. BYU kicking, 1986 November 22; 16mm film (Reel 1155-1157)
- Coach's films: games, 1986 (Box 52)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1986 November 22; 16mm film (Reel 1158-1159)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1986 November 22; 16mm film (Reel 1160-1164)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1986 November 29; 16mm film (Reel 1165-1170)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1986 November 29; 16mm film (Reel 1171-1176)
  - Utah vs. UTEP kicking, 1986 November 22; 16mm film (Reel 1177-1182)
- Coach's films: games, plays, practices and highlights, 1986-1987 (Box 53)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1986 November 29; 16mm film (Reel 1183-1186)
    Reels 2-2, 2-2, 2-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1986 November 22; 16mm film (Reel 1187)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State offense, 1986 October 25; 16mm film (Reel 1188)
  - Speed option eagle first and second whip side, 1986 March 17; 16mm film (Reel 1189)
  - Screens, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1190)
  - 14 play action, gimmick, duck, undated; 16mm film (Reel 1191)
  - Linebacker training vs. outside plays, 1986 March 06; 16mm film (Reel 1192)
  - Punt returns, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1193)
  - Reds 2-3, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1194-1195)
  - Scatter, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1196)
  - Mix team, 1987 April 28; 16mm film (Reel 1197)
  - Endzone kickoff returns, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1198)
  - Endzone punts, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1199)
  - Kickoff returns, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1199-1200)
  - Twist games and pass rush, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1201)
  - Arc option, first and second whip side, 1986 March 17; 16mm film (Reel 1202)
  - 18 gadgets, 1986; 16mm film (Reel 1203)
  - Unidentified films, undated; 16mm film (Reel 1204-1212)
- Coach's films: drills, 1987 (Box 54)
  - Defensive back drills 3, 1987 April 22; 16mm film (Reel 1213)
  - 7 on 7 vs. scout, 1987 September 15; 16mm film (Reel 1214)
  - Unidentified films, undated; 16mm film (Reel 1215-1233)
- Coach's films: plays, practices and highlights, 1987 (Box 55)
  - Scott Mitchell, University of Utah, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1234)
  - Spring practice, 1987 April 10; 16mm film (Reel 1235-1236)
  - Spring practice, 1987 April 17; 16mm film (Reel 1237)
  - R-I-T, 1987 April 22; 16mm film (Reel 1238)
  - Trap, all options 834, 1987 April 28; 16mm film (Reel 1239)
  - 7 on 7, 1987 April 28; 16mm film (Reel 1240)
  - 9 on 7, 1987 April 29; 16mm film (Reel 1241)
  - Scrimmage, 1987 April 29; 16mm film (Reel 1242)
  - Special teams, 1987 August 22; 16mm film (Reel 1243)
  - Veer pass, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1244)
  - Kickoff returns, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1245)
  - Kickoff touchbacks, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1246)
  - End zone extra points, field goals, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1247)
  - Extra points, field goals, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1248)
  - End zone place-kick defense, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1249)
  - Kickoffs, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1250)
  - End zone kickoffs, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1251)
  - Punts, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1252)
  - Kickoff returns, touchbacks, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1253)
  - Sacks, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1254)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State goal line, 1987 September 26; 16mm film (Reel 1245)
  - Utah vs. Air Force defense highlights, 1987 October 03; 16mm film (Reel 1246)
  - Orange slash, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1247)
  - 26S power, 26 power, 25 spirit draw, 40 draw, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1248)
  - 27 log, 27 counter trap, 26 log, 46 option, 22 ISO, 23 ISO, 22 O, 23 bounce, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1249)
  - 41-31 pop, 30-31 trap, 22 TT, 40 crash, 39 option, 33 veer, 18 option, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1250)
  - Red 2-3, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1251-1252)
- Coach's films: plays, practices and highlights, 1987 (Box 56)
  - Spring practice RIT, 1987 April 04; 16mm film (Reel 1253)
  - 3rd short, 1987 April 15; 16mm film (Reel 1254)
  - Spring practice, 1987 April 17; 16mm film (Reel 1255)
  - 9 on 7, 1987 April 28; 16mm film (Reel 1256)
  - University of Utah alumni game, 1987 May 02; 16mm film (Reel 1257)
    Test 125
    Asa Fuji
    Overcast day
  - Special teams, 1987 April 28; 16mm film (Reel 1258)
  - Place-kick defense, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1259)
  - Punt returns, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1260)
  - End zone punt returns, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1261)
  - Goal line runs, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1262)
  - Universal cover 3, read cover 6, cover 2, 40 double bullets, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1263)
  - Charlie, sprint run, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1264)
  - Option screens, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1265)
  - 24 give, 28 wide, 34 give, 32-33 blast, 30 drive, 30-32 express, quarterback sneak, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1266)
  - Inside run vs. slide, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1267)
  - Hawaii run, shoot options, veer drive trap, 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1268)
  - 40 double bullets, 40 regular blitz, 42 whip storm, 42 Mike slide gaps, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1269)
  - Weak side passes, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1270)
  - 28 G sweep, 28 quick pitch, 29 quick pitch, 29 pitch, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1271)
  - Blitz, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1272)
  - Dash, fire, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1273)
  - Red 1, 4, circa 1987; 16mm film (Reel 1274)
- Coach's films: games, 1987 (Box 57)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico, 1987 September 05; 16mm film (Reel 1275)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico kicking, 1987 September 05; 16mm film (Reel 1276-1277)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1987 September 05; 16mm film (Reel 1278-1281)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1987 September 05; 16mm film (Reel 1282-1286)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1987 September 12; 16mm film (Reel 1287-1290)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State defense, 1987 September 12; 16mm film (Reel 1291-1294)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State end zone defense, 1987 September 12; 16mm film (Reel 1295-1296)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State kicking, 1987 September 12; 16mm film (Reel 1297-1298)
- Coach's films: games, 1987 (Box 58)
  - Utah vs. Wisconsin offense, 1987 September 19; 16mm film (Reel 1299-1302)
  - Utah vs. Wisconsin defense, 1987 September 19; 16mm film (Reel 1303-1307)
  - Utah vs. Wisconsin kicking, 1987 September 19; 16mm film (Reel 1308-1309)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State offense, 1987 September 26; 16mm film (Reel 1310-1313)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State defense, 1987 September 26; 16mm film (Reel 1314-1319)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State kicking, 1987 September 26; 16mm film (Reel 1320-1321)
- Coach's films: games, 1987 (Box 59)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, 1987 October 03; 16mm film (Reel 1322-1325)
  - Utah vs. Air Force defense, 1987 October 03; 16mm film (Reel 1326-1330)
  - Utah vs. Air Force kicking, 1987 October 03; 16mm film (Reel 1331-1332)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, 1987 October 10; 16mm film (Reel 1333-1336)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1987 October 10; 16mm film (Reel 1337-1342)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State kicking, 1987 October 10; 16mm film (Reel 1343-1344)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii kicking, 1987 October 17; 16mm film (Reel 1345)
- Coach's films: games, 1987 (Box 60)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii kicking, 1987 October 17; 16mm film (Reel 1346)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, 1987 October 17; 16mm film (Reel 1347-1350)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii defense, 1987 October 17; 16mm film (Reel 1351-1354)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1987 October 24; 16mm film (Reel 1355-1358)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1987 October 24; 16mm film (Reel 1359-1364)
  - Utah vs. Utah State end zone, 1987 October 24; 16mm film (Reel 1365-1366)
  - Utah vs. Utah State kicking, 1987 October 24; 16mm film (Reel 1367-1368)
- Coach's films: games, 1987 (Box 61)
  - Utah vs. Boise State offense, 1987 October 31; 16mm film (Reel 1369-1373)
  - Utah vs. Boise State defense, 1987 October 31; 16mm film (Reel 1374-1378)
  - Utah vs. Boise State kicking, 1987 October 31; 16mm film (Reel 1379)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1987 November 07; 16mm film (Reel 1380-1384)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1987 November 07; 16mm film (Reel 1385-1388)
  - Utah vs. UTEP kicking, 1987 November 07; 16mm film (Reel 1389-1392)
- Coach's films: games, 1987 (Box 62)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1987 November 07; 16mm film (Reel 1393)
  - Utah vs. UTEP end zone defense, 1987 November 07; 16mm film (Reel 1394-1395)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1987 November 07; 16mm film (Reel 1396)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1987 November 14; 16mm film (Reel 1397-1403)
    Reels 1-2, 1-2, 1-2, 2-2, 2-2, 2-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1987 November 14; 16mm film (Reel 1404-1410)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming end zone defense, 1987 November 14; 16mm film (Reel 1411-1412)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1987 November 14; 16mm film (Reel 1413-1415)
- Coach's films: games, 1987 (Box 63)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1987 November 21; 16mm film (Reel 1416-1419)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1987 November 21; 16mm film (Reel 1420-1425)
  - Utah vs. BYU end zone defense, 1987 November 21; 16mm film (Reel 1426-1427)
  - Utah vs. BYU kicking, 1987 November 21; 16mm film (Reel 1428-1429)
- Coach's films: plays and practices, 1988 (Box 64)
  - Unidentified films, undated; 16mm film (Reel 1430-1436)
    These films may be:
    1-2. Utah vs. UTEP (10/01/88) kicking and offense
    3. JH 6 kicking defense
    4. Mock game kicks (8/31/85)
    5. PAPs II 1983 sprint outs and break conts
    6. 1977 punts
    7. Extra points and field goals
  - PUP, 1988 April 08; 16mm film (Reel 1437)
  - PUP, 1988 April 19; 16mm film (Reel 1438)
  - PUP, 1988 April 26; 16mm film (Reel 1439)
  - Perimeter drill, 1988 April 26; 16mm film (Reel 1440)
  - Scrum, 1988 April 27; 16mm film (Reel 1441-1442)
  - Team thud, 1988 April 29; 16mm film (Reel 1443)
  - 9 on 7 offense, 1988 May 03; 16mm film (Reel 1444)
  - 1, 1988 May 05; 16mm film (Reel 1445)
  - 9 on 7 vs. 50, 1988 Spring; 16mm film (Reel 1446)
  - Spring game extra points and vield goals vs. PKD, 1988; 16mm film (Reel 1447)
  - Spring scrum, 1988; 16mm film (Reel 1448)
  - Blitz vs. run, pass, 1988 Spring; 16mm film (Reel 1449)
  - Red area scrum, 1988 Spring; 16mm film (Reel 1450)
  - Stunt games vs. run, 1988 Spring; 16mm film (Reel 1451)
  - Open games vs. run, 1988 Spring; 16mm film (Reel 1452)
- Coach's films: spring practice, games, 1988 (Box 65)
  - 7 on 7, 1988 April 06; 16mm film (Reel 1453)
  - PUP, 1988 April 22; 16mm film (Reel 1454)
  - PUP, 1988 April 27; 16mm film (Reel 1455)
  - PUP, 1988 Spring; 16mm film (Reel 1456)
  - Eagle Okie stunts vs. run, pass, circa 1988; 16mm film (Reel 1457)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State offense, 1988 September 10; 16mm film (Reel 1458-1461)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State defense, 1988 September 10; 16mm film (Reel 1463-1469)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State kicking, 1988 September 10; 16mm film (Reel 1470-1471)
    Reels 1-1, 1-1
  - Utah vs. Illinois kicking, 1988 September 17; 16mm film (Reel 1472)
- Coach's films: games, 1988 (Box 66)
  - Utah vs. Illinois kicking, 1988 September 17; 16mm film (Reel 1473)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, 1988 September 24; 16mm film (Reel 1474-1477)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii defense, 1988 September 24; 16mm film (Reel 1478-1479)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii kicking, 1988 September 24; 16mm film (Reel 1480-1481)
  - Utah vs. UTEP kicking, 1988 October 01; 16mm film (Reel 1482-1483)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1988 October 01; 16mm film (Reel 1484-1488)
- Coach's films: plays and practices, 1988 (Box 67)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1988 October 01; 16mm film (Reel 1489)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1988 October 08; 16mm film (Reel 1490-1493)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1988 October 08; 16mm film (Reel 1494-1497)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico kicking, 1988 October 08; 16mm film (Reel 1498-1499)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, 1988 October 15; 16mm film (Reel 1500-1501)
  - Utah vs. Air Force defense, 1988 October 15; 16mm film (Reel 1502-1505)
  - Utah vs. Air Force kicking, 1988 October 15; 16mm film (Reel 1506-1507)
  - Unidentified film, undated; 16mm film (Reel 1508)
    Possibly Utah vs. Wyoming (10/22/88) or blast, express
- Coach's films: games, 1988 (Box 68)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1988 October 22; 16mm film (Reel 1509-1512)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1988 October 22; 16mm film (Reel 1513-1516)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1988 October 22; 16mm film (Reel 1517-1518)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1988 October 29; 16mm film (Reel 1519-1522)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State defense, 1988 October 29; 16mm film (Reel 1523-1526)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State kicking, 1988 October 29; 16mm film (Reel 1527-1528)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State kicking, 1988 November 05; 16mm film (Reel 1529-1530)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, 1988 November 05; 16mm film (Reel 1531-1532)
- Coach's films: games, 1988 (Box 69)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, 1988 November 05; 16mm film (Reel 1533-1534)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1988 November 05; 16mm film (Reel 1535-1538)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1988 November 12; 16mm film (Reel 1539-1540)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1988 November 12; 16mm film (Reel 1541-1542)
  - Utah vs. Utah State kicking, 1988 November 12; 16mm film (Reel 1543)
- Coach's films: games, 1988 (Box 70)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State offense, 1988 September 10; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1544-1545)
    End zone, unlabeled
  - Utah vs. Idaho State defense, 1988 September 10; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1545-1546)
    End zone, wide
  - Utah vs. Illinois offense, 1988 September 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1547)
    Wide
  - Utah vs. Illinois defense, 1988 September 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1548-1549)
    Wide, end zone
  - Utah vs. Illinois special teams, 1988 September 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1550-1551)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, 1988 September 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1552)
    End zone
  - Utah vs. Hawaii defense, 1988 September 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1553-1554)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1988 October 01; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1555-1556)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1988 October 01; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1557-1558)
  - Utah vs. UTEP special teams, 1988 October 01; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1559-1560)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1988 October 08; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1561-1562)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1988 October 08; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1563-1564)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico special teams, 1988 October 08; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1565-1566)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, 1988 October 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1567)
  - Utah vs. Air Force defense, 1988 October 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1568)
  - Utah vs. Air Force special teams, 1988 October 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1569-1570)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1988 October 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1571)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1988 October 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1572-1573)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming special teams, 1988 October 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1574-1575)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State defense, 1988 October 29; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1576-1577)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State special teams, 1988 October 29; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1578-1579)
- Coach's films: games, 1988-1989 (Box 71)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State special teams, 1988 November 05; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1580-1581)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1988 November 05; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1582-1583)
  - Utah vs. Utah State special teams, 1988 November 12; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1582-1583)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1988 November 12; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1584)
    End zone/wide
  - Utah vs. BYU, 1988 November 19; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1585-1586)
    Tapes 1-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1988 November 19; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1587)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1988 November 19; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1588-1589)
  - Utah vs. BYU special teams, 1988 November 19; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1590-1591)
  - Utah vs. Fresno State offense, 1989 September 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1592-1593)
  - Utah vs. Fresno State defense, 1989 September 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1594-1595)
  - Utah vs. Fresno State special teams, 1989 September 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1596-1597)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1989 September 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1598)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1989 September 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1599-1600)
  - Utah vs. Utah State special teams, 1989 September 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1601-1603)
    2 end zone, 1 wide
  - Utah vs. Nebraska offense, 1989 September 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1604-1605)
  - Utah vs. Nebraska defense, 1989 September 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1606)
  - Utah vs. Nebraska special teams, 1989 September 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1607-1608)
  - Utah vs. Nebraska offense, defense, special teams, 1989 September 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1609)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, 1989 September 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1606-1607)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii defense, 1989 September 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1608-1609)
    2 wide
  - Utah vs. Hawaii special teams, 1989 September 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1610-1611)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, defense, kicking, 1989 September 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1612-1613)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State, 1989 September 30; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1614)
- Coach's films: games, 1989 (Box 72)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1989 September 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1615-1616)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State defense, 1989 September 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1617-1618)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State special teams, 1989 September 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1619-1620)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1989 October 07; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1621-1622)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1989 October 07; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1623-1624)
  - Utah vs. UTEP special teams, 1989 October 07; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1625)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1989 October 14; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1626-1627)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1989 October 14; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1628-1629)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming special teams, 1989 October 14; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1630-1631)
  - Utah vs. Stanford offense, 1989 October 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1632)
  - Utah vs. Stanford offense, 1989 October 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1633)
    From Stanford
  - Utah vs. Stanford defense, 1989 October 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1634)
  - Utah vs. Stanford defense, 1989 October 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1635)
  - Utah vs. Stanford special teams, 1989 October 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1636)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, 1989 October 28; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1637-1638)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1989 October 28; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1639-1640)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State special teams, 1989 October 28; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1641-1642)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1989 November 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1643-1644)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1989 November 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1645-1646)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico special teams, 1989 November 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1647-1648)
  - Scott Mitchell: All-American candidate, circa 1989; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1649)
- Coach's films: games, 1989-1990 (Box 73)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1989 November 18; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1650-1652)
    Wide, end zone, wide and end zone
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1989 November 18; VHS videocassette (Cassette 163-1654)
  - Utah vs. BYU special teams, 1989 November 18; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1655-1656)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, 1989 November 25; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1657-1658)
  - Utah vs. Air Force defense, 1989 November 25; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1659-1660)
  - Utah vs. Air Force special teams, 1989 November 25; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1661-1662)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1990 September 01; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1663-1665)
    2 wide, 1 end zone
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1990 September 01; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1666-1667)
  - Utah vs. Utah State special teams, 1990 September 01; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1668-1670)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, special teams, 1990 September 01; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1671)
    End zone and wide
  - Utah vs. Minnesota offense, defense, special teams, 1990 September 08; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1672)
  - Utah vs. Minnesota defense, 1990 September 08; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1673-1674)
  - Utah vs. Minnesota special teams, 1990 September 08; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1675-1678)
    4 wide
  - Utah vs. Fresno State offense, 1990 September 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1679-1681)
  - Utah vs. Fresno State defense, 1990 September 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1682-1683)
  - Utah vs. Fresno State special teams, 1990 September 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1684-1686)
  - Utah vs. BYU pre-game show, 1990; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1687)
    Feature about Utah linebacker Anthony Dixon
  - Utah football, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1688)
- Coach's films: games, 1990 (Box 74)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, 1990 September 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1689-1690)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii defense, 1990 September 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1691-1692)